Hello
hello friends, I am Mahavir and today
I am going to tell you about the company for term investment. The
name of that company is
ICICI Lombard General Insurance.
Why has the company chosen for long-term investment? There are four to five
reasons for this. First is its profit, which is the
profit growth of the last three to ten years. At point number 2, do
not forget to subscribe and
subscribe.
Accordingly, its number will come up and I will
see the technical aspects.
Now before proceeding with the video, I
want to tell you one thing that this is not my
recommendation of any kind of fraud.
Before making any kind of investment, please check it once as per your understanding
and then
invest in it. Even then, first of all we will
see the profit growth of the company. We will
come down here and you can see this profit here.
Now let us see the growth in the last three years,
hence
subscribe but the profit growth of the last three years is 0.
Subscribe and
subscribe,
subscribe, according to this, you
can break this company down. At number two is its
profit growth of the last 10 years.  The annual
profit growth average
is 25%, the last five years is 2001
but looking at the last 3 years it
is growing from 2036 subscribe and both these things are
very good, that is why I have
considered it as an investment
and the second good thing about it is its ROC,
so the last three years' rate is just 18 percent,
where if you see in comparison to other companies,
HDFC Life Insurance
's 3-year return is 200 and SBI
Life's is 19 percent, in front of that
ICICI Bank has 8 percent, this is also
a very good thing, in its peer comparison, it is such a
big company, in that
this company has given the best return of capital employed
and if we see, the
debt-equity ratio of the company is 0.65 and the company is
trading at a PE of 50, the
other company in comparison to it is doing great history of 113
and SBI Life is
trading at a PE of 5.3, in
front of it is ICICI Lombard.  It is
trading at a PE of 50, this is also a
good and big plus point for it. If
we look at the promoter holding here, there is 14% promoter
holding which can be considered quite good. If
we look at the building pattern in more detail, then the
promoter holding is 48%. If we
click on the total thirteen percent near the 2017 peak of ASI, then
see here,
one is that Building Private Limited,
it has 3.72 processors and this is
Society Benzene, which has
5570 i.e. seven to eight percent out of 13,
so both of them have it, that is,
only 5 to 6 percent is with the general public, according to
this pattern it
seems that you can also
apply for investment,
now we will take a look at the mutual fund holding of the company, for this
we will come to
Rupesh Kumar and here by going to the
search bar, I have written the name of the company,
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance and here if we click on search, then
something like this  The result will be in front of us, so
look at this, the swift shoulder of the last 4 months is in
front of us,
from 4 crore 39 lakh in August 2002, Total Mutual Fund has
increased to 56001 in November,
this number
subscribe
sure which is maintained by ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Holding, it seems that the total is around
200, so
how much is this worth in this, Subscribe Subscribe,
so here we can clearly
see that mutual funds are also
very interested in it,
now let us take a look at its technical chart and
put it above, and see,
we have deleted it in front of us, this
is the daily chart in front of us and if we look at it in the long term, then from
2017 till now 2021, it is continuously
opposing you, that is clearly visible,
now if we see if there is a decline in this company, then by
how much percentage does it fall,
so see this, if we look at it from here,
till here, the first decline they saw
was Meena  20 percent after that we will
check it again from here this was the second time it was
called so till here and at
21 evening param priya had come close to 21 percent
after this we will check it for the third time here here
seventeen percent the company has
set an alarm dept after that this one point
pendant this one will
fold it a little bit after that we will look here so
see here this Trump had
shown a dance of thirteen percent after that
we will look here again so see from
here he showed here
1872 don't set but every side every time
after the dancer the company comes back by protesting look here
from here we will read
resident Vishnu has started walking and this is
his leg sent and right now this is the dance
we are seeing here so
see here we are seeing this he stands straight for half an inch
you are seeing
subscribed after that it starts again
from the top I think
this is the best time for us to enter in
this  You can invest money Hussain,
if we look here,
after putting here, see from here to here, the company had
shown good growth of this question within a day, after that you can see this company
Samsung and here if we
can see from here to here, then
friends, within 40 days, the
cent off on appointment is shown,
subscribe here, pumping office came
and from here to here, 40 cent
off is
shown here, that too within a day, after that
see,
subscribe here and from here to here,
subscribe
Indian
more is shown, after that back to the company
and see that the return companies in this
happened in less than 18 years, after that
you can take this company here, if you
want to take it for short term, then you can also take this thumb,
see, this is only 16 percent within 40 to 45 days,
now this
is not a small return, if you get the full 16 percent
in 6 months, 8 months or
even a year, then it is considered a very good return, so in
this way you can also earn within two or three
years.  If you take it and invest 10-20 per cent,
then
you can easily earn 30 to 40 per cent in a single company within the whole year.
If you liked all this information, then
similar videos keep
coming on my channel. Please
like and subscribe to the youth channel.
Thank you so much.